<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Train the Models on IBM CloudPak for Watson AIOps - Training</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Train the Models on IBM CloudPak for Watson AIOps - Training</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>http://example.org/introduction/intro_00/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/introduction/intro_00/</guid>
      <description> Introduction In this Training you will learn how to install IBM CloudPak for AIOps and how to configure some basic functionnalities.
The idea is to provide an optimised way for you to learn CP4WAIOPS.
In the end you will have a demo environment containing the following components:
AI Manager OpenLDAP registered with AI Manager AWX (Open Source Ansible Tower) with Playbooks and CP4WAIOPS Runbooks AI Models for Log Anomaly Detectiom Metric Anomaly Detection Event Grouping Similar Incidents Change Risk Topology RobotShop Demo Installation K8s Observer RobotShop Application </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Architecture</title>
      <link>http://example.org/introduction/intro_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/introduction/intro_01/</guid>
      <description>Basic Architecture The environement (Kubernetes, Applications, &amp;hellip;) create logs that are being fed into a Log Management Tool (ELK in this case).
External Systems generate Alerts and send them into the AI Manager for Event Grouping. At the same time AI Manager ingests the raw logs coming from the Log Management Tool (ELK) and looks for anomalies in the stream based on the trained model. It also ingests Metric Data and looks for anomalies If it finds an anomaly (logs and/or metrics) it forwards it to the Event Grouping as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training Architecture</title>
      <link>http://example.org/introduction/intro_02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/introduction/intro_02/</guid>
      <description> Optimized Training Architecture For the this specific Demo environment:
ELK is installed for you to kearn how to integrate it For Log Anomaly simulation we&amp;rsquo;ll beusing pre-canned logs for the anomaly detection (inception) For Metrics, we&amp;rsquo;ll be using pre-canned metric data for training and for the anomaly detection (inception) The Events will be created from pre-canned content that is injected into AI Manager There are also pre-canned ServiceNow Incidents as we don’t do the live integration with SNOW for this training The Webpages that are reachable from the Events are static and hosted on my GitHub The same goes for ServiceNow Incident pages if you don’t integrate with live SNOW </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get your Cluster</title>
      <link>http://example.org/prerequisites/prereq_00/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/prerequisites/prereq_00/</guid>
      <description>Get your ROKS Cluster (IBMers and IBM Partners only) IBMers can get a temporary one from Techzone (ususally valid for up to 8 days)
Create a cluster for Practice/Self Education if you don&amp;rsquo;t have an Opportunity Number
Select the maximum end date that fits your needs (you can extend the duration once after creation)
Fill-in the remaining fields
Geograpy: prefer Dallas or London (others might be slower) Worker node count: 5 Flavour: b3c.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Important remarks</title>
      <link>http://example.org/prerequisites/prereq_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/prerequisites/prereq_01/</guid>
      <description>⚠️⚠️ Important remarks before you start ⚠️⚠️ Those are remarks regarding feedback and problem reports I got from the field.
Those scripts have been tested thoroughly on different environments and have proven to be VERY reliable.
If you think that you hit a problem:
Make sure that you have provisioned a cluster with 5 worker nodes with 16 CPU and 64 GB each (b3c.16x64 - it&amp;rsquo;s easy to select the wrong size).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing to run commands</title>
      <link>http://example.org/installing-operator/install_aimanager_00/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/installing-operator/install_aimanager_00/</guid>
      <description>Preparing to run commands The official documentation can be found here.
Befor continuing, you have to connect to your OpenShift Cluster.
Open your Openshift Web Console
Select Copy Login Command
Copy the oc login .. string
Open your terminal
Paste the oc login .. command from above
Clone the GitHub Repository into your directory of choice
git clone https://github.com/niklaushirt/cp4waiops-deployer.git Go to the deployer directory
cd cp4waiops-deployer Now you&amp;rsquo;re good to start with the installation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing Installation</title>
      <link>http://example.org/installing-operator/install_aimanager_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/installing-operator/install_aimanager_01/</guid>
      <description>Preparing Installation Create the namespace (project) Create a namespace called cp4waiops, by running the following command:
oc create namespace cp4waiops Create the OperatorGroup Create the Operator group by running the following command:
cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt; EOF | oc apply -f - apiVersion: operators.coreos.com/v1 kind: OperatorGroup metadata: name: cp4waiops-operator-group namespace: cp4waiops spec: targetNamespaces: - cp4waiops EOF Create the entitlement key pull secret Log in to MyIBM Container Software Library with the IBMid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Catalog</title>
      <link>http://example.org/installing-operator/install_aimanager_02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/installing-operator/install_aimanager_02/</guid>
      <description>Installing the Catalog Run the following command to create the CatalogSource.
cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt; EOF | oc apply -f - apiVersion: operators.coreos.com/v1alpha1 kind: CatalogSource metadata: name: ibm-operator-catalog namespace: openshift-marketplace spec: displayName: ibm-operator-catalog publisher: IBM Content sourceType: grpc image: icr.io/cpopen/ibm-operator-catalog:latest EOF Update the CatalogSource to always use the current image digest by running the following commands:
IMGDIGEST=`oc get pods -n openshift-marketplace -l=olm.catalogSource=ibm-operator-catalog --no-headers -o=jsonpath=&amp;#34;{.items[0].status.containerStatuses[0].imageID}&amp;#34; -n openshift-marketplace` &amp;amp;&amp;amp; \ oc patch catalogsource ibm-operator-catalog -n openshift-marketplace --type=json -p &amp;#34;[{ &amp;#34;op&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;test&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;path&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;/spec/image&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;value&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;\&amp;#34;icr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Operator</title>
      <link>http://example.org/installing-operator/install_aimanager_03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/installing-operator/install_aimanager_03/</guid>
      <description>Installing the Operator Run the following command:
cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt; EOF | oc apply -f - apiVersion: operators.coreos.com/v1alpha1 kind: Subscription metadata: name: ibm-aiops-orchestrator namespace: cp4waiops spec: channel: v3.5 installPlanApproval: Automatic name: ibm-aiops-orchestrator source: ibm-operator-catalog sourceNamespace: openshift-marketplace EOF ``</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check Installation</title>
      <link>http://example.org/installing-operator/install_aimanager_04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/installing-operator/install_aimanager_04/</guid>
      <description>Check Operator is ready Verify that the Operator is running.
Either run the following: oc get csv -n cp4waiops And you should see TODO entries with Succeeded state
NAME DISPLAY VERSION REPLACES PHASE aimanager-operator.v3.5.1 IBM Watson AIOps AI Manager 3.5.1 Succeeded aiopsedge-operator.v3.5.1 IBM Watson AIOps Edge 3.5.1 Succeeded asm-operator.v3.5.1 IBM Netcool Agile Service Manager 3.5.1 Succeeded elasticsearch-operator.5.5.3 OpenShift Elasticsearch Operator 5.5.3 Succeeded ibm-aiops-ir-ai.v3.5.1 IBM Watson AIOps Issue Resolution AI &amp;amp; Analytics 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install AI Manager</title>
      <link>http://example.org/installing-ai-manager/install_aimanager_00/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/installing-ai-manager/install_aimanager_00/</guid>
      <description>Creating the AI Manager Instance Run the following command to create an instance of AI Manager.
cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt; EOF | oc apply -f - apiVersion: orchestrator.aiops.ibm.com/v1alpha1 kind: Installation metadata: name: ibm-cp-watson-aiops namespace: cp4waiops spec: imagePullSecret: ibm-entitlement-key license: accept: true pakModules: - name: aiopsFoundation enabled: true - name: applicationManager enabled: true - name: aiManager enabled: true - name: connection enabled: false size: small storageClass: ibmc-file-gold-gid storageClassLargeBlock: ibmc-block-gold EOF This takes some time depending on what region of ROKS you have chosen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check Installation</title>
      <link>http://example.org/installing-ai-manager/install_aimanager_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/installing-ai-manager/install_aimanager_01/</guid>
      <description>Check AI Manager is ready ❗ This takes some time depending on what region of ROKS you have chosen. Wait up to 45 minutes for the installation to complete.
Check with the Command Line Run the following:
oc get po -n cp4waiops | grep -v Completed | grep -v Error |grep &amp;#34;0/&amp;#34; oc get po -n cp4waiops | grep -v Completed | grep -v Error |grep -v &amp;#34;0/&amp;#34; |wc -l| tr -d &amp;#39; &amp;#39; oc get po -n cp4waiops | grep -v Completed | grep -v Error |grep &amp;#34;0/&amp;#34; |wc -l| tr -d &amp;#39; &amp;#39; This will list the Pods that are not Ready yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>http://example.org/installing-training-resources/install_aimanager_00/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/installing-training-resources/install_aimanager_00/</guid>
      <description>Installing Training resources This will install resources that you will need for the configuration of AI Manager in the next chapter.
Those are assets that typically already exist at a customer.
OpenLDAP AWX (Open Source Ansible Tower) with preloaded Playbooks RobotShop Demo App Demo Service Account This will also load training data for:
Log Anomalies
You will integrate with your live ELK instance but you probably don&amp;rsquo;t have 2-3 days to wait for ELK to collect enough logs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Training Resources</title>
      <link>http://example.org/installing-training-resources/install_aimanager_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/installing-training-resources/install_aimanager_01/</guid>
      <description>Installing Training resources Run the following code to start the creation of the Training Resources.
cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt; EOF | oc apply -f - kind: ClusterRoleBinding apiVersion: rbac.authorization.k8s.io/v1 metadata: name: installer-default-default roleRef: apiGroup: rbac.authorization.k8s.io kind: ClusterRole name: cluster-admin subjects: - kind: ServiceAccount name: default namespace: default --- apiVersion: batch/v1 kind: Job metadata: name: waiops-easy-install-aimanager-practicum namespace: default spec: serviceAccountName: installer-default-default template: spec: containers: - name: install image: niklaushirt/cp4waiops-tools:1.3 imagePullPolicy: IfNotPresent resources: requests: memory: &amp;#34;64Mi&amp;#34; cpu: &amp;#34;150m&amp;#34; limits: memory: &amp;#34;1256Mi&amp;#34; cpu: &amp;#34;1200m&amp;#34; command: - /bin/sh - -c - | #!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check Installation</title>
      <link>http://example.org/installing-training-resources/install_aimanager_02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/installing-training-resources/install_aimanager_02/</guid>
      <description> Check Training Resources are ready ❗ This takes some time depending on what region of ROKS you have chosen. Wait up to 45 minutes for the installation to complete.
You can follow along the process by running:
./tools/11_fzth/stream_remote_logs.sh Or through the OpensHift Web Console:
Select default Namespace
Select Pods
Click on the waiops-easy-install-aimanager-practicum-... Pod
Select Logs
🚀 And when done you should get the following with failed=0.
PLAY RECAP ********************************************************************* localhost : ok=XXX changed=XXX unreachable=0 failed=0 skipped=XXX rescued=0 ignored=0 ***************************************************************************************************************************** ✅ DONE ***************************************************************************************************************************** </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get the information</title>
      <link>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_00/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_00/</guid>
      <description> Get the configuration information Run the following command to create an instance of AI Manager. ./tools/11_fzth/get_configuration_info.sh This will provide you with all the information and details that you need to configure AI Manager in this chapter.
⚠️ You can also save the information to a file to keep it handy
./tools/11_fzth/get_configuration_info.sh &amp;gt; MY_CONFIGURATION.txt </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Login</title>
      <link>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_01/</guid>
      <description>Login to AI Manager In your OpenShift Console click on the Applications Menu
Select CP4WAIOps Demo UI
Login with token P4ssw0rd!
Copy the Admin Password
Open AI Manager
Select IBM provided credentials
Login with admin user and the password you copied in the step above
Welcome to AI Manager</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initialize ELK</title>
      <link>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_02/</guid>
      <description>Initialize ELK In your OpenShift Console click on the Applications Menu
Select Logging
Accept default values
Input app* for the index pattern
Click Next Step
Select @timestamp for time filter
Click Create Index Pattern
ELK is now configured. Verify that you have Logs coming in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure LDAP</title>
      <link>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_03/</guid>
      <description>Configure LDAP integration Create LDAP provider In the AI Manager &amp;ldquo;Hamburger&amp;rdquo; Menu select Access Control
In the top right Click Identity provider configuration
You might have to re-login with your admin user
In the top right Click New Connection
Select LDAP from the dropdown
Click Next
🔎 Get the data from your configuration info - section 2.1 Configure LDAP
./tools/11_fzth/get_configuration_info.sh Fill out the first section of fields:
Connection name: LDAP Server type: Custom Base DN: dc=ibm,dc=com Bind DN: cn=admin,dc=ibm,dc=com Bind DN password: P4ssw0rd!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure ELK</title>
      <link>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_04/</guid>
      <description>Configure ELK In the AI Manager &amp;ldquo;Hamburger&amp;rdquo; Menu select Define/Data and tool integrations
Click Add connection
Under ELK, click on Add connection
Click Connect
Name it ELK
🔎 Get the data from your configuration info - section 2.2 Configure asdfdsafdsa
./tools/11_fzth/get_configuration_info.sh Fill out the fields on the first page:
ELK service URL: from script Authentication type: Token Token: from script Kibana URL: from script Kibana port: 443 Mapping: { &amp;#34;codec&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;elk&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;message_field&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;message&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;log_entity_types&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;kubernete	s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Runbooks</title>
      <link>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_05/</guid>
      <description>Configure Runbooks Create Ansible Tower Connection In the AI Manager &amp;ldquo;Hamburger&amp;rdquo; Menu select Define/Data and tool integrations
Click Add connection
Under Ansible Automation Controller, click on Add connection
Click Connect
🔎 Get the data from your configuration info - section 2.3 Configure Runbooks - Ansible Automation Controller
./tools/11_fzth/get_configuration_info.sh Fill out the fields:
URL for REST API: from script Authentication type: User ID/Password User: admin Password: from script ``
Click Done</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Policies</title>
      <link>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_06/</guid>
      <description>Configure Policies Enable Story creation Policy In the AI Manager &amp;ldquo;Hamburger&amp;rdquo; Menu select Operate/Automations
Select tab Policies
Click on the Tag dropdown
Select Stories and Runbooks
Turn on Policy Default story creation policy for all alerts
Create Runbook Assignment Policy Click on Create Policy
Click on Assign a runbook to alerts
Name it RobotShop Mitigate MySQL Problem
Scroll down to Condition sets
Click in field Property
Type name
Select resource / name</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Applications</title>
      <link>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_07/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/configure-ai-manager/configure_aimanager_07/</guid>
      <description>Create Kubernetes Observer In the AI Manager &amp;ldquo;Hamburger&amp;rdquo; Menu select Define/Data and tool integrations
Click Add connection
Under Kubernetes, click on Add connection
Click Connect
🔎 Get the data from your configuration info - section 2.5 Configure Applications - RobotShop Kubernetes Observer
./tools/11_fzth/get_configuration_info.sh Fill out the first section of fields (Add connection):
Name: RobotShop Data center: robot-shop Click Next
Fill out the first section of fields (Set advanced options):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Log Anomalies</title>
      <link>http://example.org/train-the-models/configure_aimanager_00/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/train-the-models/configure_aimanager_00/</guid>
      <description>Define Log Anomalies Training In the AI Manager &amp;ldquo;Hamburger&amp;rdquo; Menu select Operate/AI Model Management
Under Log anomaly detection - natural language, click on Set up training
Click Next
Under Select data check Custom
Select Start date as March, 3rd 2022
Select End date as March, 4rd 2022
Click Next
Click Next
Click Next
Under Deployment type check On completion
Click Done
Run Log Anomalies Training Click on the three dots in the upper right corner of the Log anomaly detection - natural language card</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metric Anomalies</title>
      <link>http://example.org/train-the-models/configure_aimanager_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/train-the-models/configure_aimanager_01/</guid>
      <description> Define Metric Anomalies Training In the AI Manager &amp;ldquo;Hamburger&amp;rdquo; Menu select Operate/AI Model Management Under Metric anomaly detection, click on Set up training Click Next Click Next Click Done Run Metric Anomalies Training Click on the three dots in the upper right corner of the Metric anomaly detection card Select Start Training Status should say In progress And eventually say Deployed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Similar Incidents</title>
      <link>http://example.org/train-the-models/configure_aimanager_02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/train-the-models/configure_aimanager_02/</guid>
      <description> Define Similar Incidents Training In the AI Manager &amp;ldquo;Hamburger&amp;rdquo; Menu select Operate/AI Model Management Under Similar Incidents, click on Set up training Click Next Click Next Click Done Run Similar Incidents Training Click on the three dots in the upper right corner of the Similar Incidents card Select Start Training Status should say In progress And eventually say Deployed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change Risk</title>
      <link>http://example.org/train-the-models/configure_aimanager_03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/train-the-models/configure_aimanager_03/</guid>
      <description> Define Change Risk Training In the AI Manager &amp;ldquo;Hamburger&amp;rdquo; Menu select Operate/AI Model Management Under Change Risk, click on Set up training Click Next Click Next Under Deployment type check On completion Click Done Run Change Risk Training Click on the three dots in the upper right corner of the Change Risk card Select Start Training Status should say In progress And eventually say Deployed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Grouping</title>
      <link>http://example.org/train-the-models/configure_aimanager_04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/train-the-models/configure_aimanager_04/</guid>
      <description> Define Temporal Grouping Training In the AI Manager &amp;ldquo;Hamburger&amp;rdquo; Menu select Operate/AI Model Management Under Temporal Grouping, click on Set up training Click Next Click Next Click Done Run Temporal Grouping Training Click on the three dots in the upper right corner of the Temporal Grouping card Select Start Training Status should say In progress And eventually say Deployed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check Training</title>
      <link>http://example.org/train-the-models/configure_aimanager_05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/train-the-models/configure_aimanager_05/</guid>
      <description>Check Training Status Check your Training Cards. All should be green and say Deployed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Test Incident</title>
      <link>http://example.org/test-and-demo/configure_aimanager_00/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/test-and-demo/configure_aimanager_00/</guid>
      <description>Create Test Incident In your OpenShift Console click on the Applications Menu
Select CP4WAIOps Demo UI
Login with token P4ssw0rd!
Click on Create Incident Memory Leak
Wait for pop-up to go away and the Demo UI going back to the homepage</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Examine the Incident</title>
      <link>http://example.org/test-and-demo/configure_aimanager_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/test-and-demo/configure_aimanager_01/</guid>
      <description>Examine the Incident In the AI Manager &amp;ldquo;Hamburger&amp;rdquo; Menu select Operate/Stories and Alerts
Click on Alerts
You should see some Alerts coming in
Click on Stories
You should see some Stories
Click on the first Story in the list (it should be P2 or P1 but the name can differ)
You should see some Stories
You should see the detail of the Story, with the Probable Cause, the Runbooks and the Similar Incidents</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clear the Incident</title>
      <link>http://example.org/test-and-demo/configure_aimanager_02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/test-and-demo/configure_aimanager_02/</guid>
      <description>Clear the Incident Go back to the Demo UI
Click on Clear Stories and Events
Wait for pop-up to go away and the Demo UI going back to the homepage
The Alerts will be Closed and the Stories Resolved
You will have to wait for about 10 minutes for them to disappear (you can recreate the incident earlier, which will just re-open the existing Stories )</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the IBM CloudPak for AIOps Training In this Training you will learn how to install IBM CloudPak for AIOps and how to configure some basic functionnalities.
The idea is to provide an optimised way for you to learn CP4WAIOPS.
In the end you will have a demo environment containing the following components:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
